Local 1199 Publications 6209 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Publications
1957-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199
6209 PUBS
4.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications.
6190095
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, December 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Medical personnel -- Labor unions -- Publications; Local 1199 Drug, Hospital, and Health Care Employees Union (New York, N.Y.); National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees; Service Employees International Union
6190095
- 1190 Drug News Twenty Fifth Anniversary Issue, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 1199 Drug News Twenty Fifth Anniversary Issue., 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Moe Foner; William CAHN; Stanley Glaubach
    Notes: Photocopy.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: 1199 Drug News Twenty Fifth Anniversary Issue., 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Photocopy. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 1199 Drug News Twenty Fifth Anniversary Issue., 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: Photocopy. Copy 3.
- 1199 News, 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Local 1199
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1993:Jan.)
  - Item 2: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1993:Mar.)
  - Item 3: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.4 (1993:Apr.)
  - Item 4: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.6 (1993:June)
  - Item 5: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.7/8 (1993:July/Aug.)
  - Item 6: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.7/8 (1993:July/Aug.). Copy 2.
- 1199 News, 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1993:Sept.)
  - Item 2: 1199 Delegates' News., 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1993:Oct.)
- The Working American, 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1199 Delegates' News., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1994:Feb.)
  - Item 2: 1199 Delegates' News., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1994:Apr.)
  - Item 3: 1199 Delegates' News., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1994:June)
- It's In Your Hands, 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Working American., 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Patricia Hills; Moe Foner; Abigail Booth Gerdts
    Notes: An Exhibition organized by District 1199 and the Smithsonian Institute
  - Item 2: The Working American., 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: An Exhibition organized by District 1199 and the Smithsonian Institute. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Working American., 1979; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: An Exhibition organized by District 1199 and the Smithsonian Institute. Copy 3.
- 1199 Delegates' News, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: It's In Your Hands., 1991; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Local 1199. Adult Education Program.
    Notes: Produced by participants in the Adult Education Program of 1199
- 1199 Delegates' News, 1993; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 1199 News., 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1976:Sept.). Special issue. Photocopy.
  - Item 2: 1199 News., 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1976:Sept.). Special issue. Photocopy. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 1199 News., 1976; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1976:Sept.). Special issue. Photocopy. Copy 3.
- Weekly Memorandum, 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: 1199 News., 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November, 1978.
  - Item 2: 1199 News., 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November, 1978. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: 1199 News., 1978; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: November, 1978. Copy 3.
- New Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Weekly Memorandum., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 30 - February 5, 1994.
  - Item 2: Weekly Memorandum., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: February 7-13, 1994.
  - Item 3: Weekly Memorandum., 1994; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 7-13, 1994.
- News Clippings, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: RNs Facing New Danger at Work, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: American Journal of Nursing
    Notes: October, 1995.
  - Item 2: Cutbacks in Retiree Health Coverage, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Business and Health
  - Item 3: Hosp Group Fears Medi-Job Axing, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Mark Mooney
    Notes: Daily News, October, 1995.
  - Item 4: NY Senators Offer Medicare, Medcaid Amendments, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Greater New York Hospital Association (GNYHA)
    Notes: Skyline News, 95-21 (1995:Oct. 9)
  - Item 5: House of Representatives Releases Medicare Bill, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: GNYHA to Host Health Care Forum, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: House Passes Medicare Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: HANYS (Healthcare Association of New York State)
    Notes: Continuing Care Connection, v.2:no.21 (1995:Oct. 25)
  - Item 8: HANYS Meets With White House Staff, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Certificate of Need Intake Log, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Health Systems Agency of New York City
    Notes: November 1, 1995.
  - Item 10: News at Deadline, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Hospitals and Health Networks
    Notes: October 20, 1995.
  - Item 11: Currents, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: The Presence of Medicare HMOs Lowers Costs in the Medicare Fee-For-Service Program, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Group Health Association of America
    Notes: October 10, 1995.
  - Item 13: NYC Drops Waiver Request, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Modern Healthcare
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, November 2, 1995.
  - Item 14: Credit Care Firms Charge Into Healthcare, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Sandy Lutz
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, October 30, 1995.
  - Item 15: Wall Street Questions New Networks, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Eric Weissenstein
  - Item 16: Bellevue Seeks Independence From City, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Barbara Benson
    Notes: Crain's New York Business, October 1, 1995
  - Item 17: State to Lose $19 Billion in GOP's Medicaid Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Alice Lipowicz
  - Item 18: HIP Sells 2 Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Crain's New York Business
    Notes: Crain's New York Business, September 18, 1995.
  - Item 19: House GOP Leadership Releases Medicare Outline, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.38 (1995:Sep. 22).
  - Item 20: Repubilcan Medicare and Medicaid Plans Only Days Away, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.37 (1995:Sep. 15).
  - Item 21: Congress Set to Make Massive Medicare and Medicaid Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.36 (1995:Sep. 8).
  - Item 22: Certificate of Need Intake Log, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: October 1, 1995.
  - Item 23: Improving Materials Management Through Re-Engineering, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Christopher M. Born; Dan Marino
    Notes: Healthcare Financial Management, September, 1995.
  - Item 24: Boxed In?, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Chuck Appleby
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, September 20, 1995.
  - Item 25: Evaluating Unlicensed Assistive Personnel Models, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Joan M. K. Russo; Diane R. Lancaster
    Notes: JONA, v.25:no.9 (1995:Sep.).
  - Item 26: ANA Fires Back at Calif. Secessionists, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, September 25, 1995.
  - Item 27: LA Nurses Stage Sickout, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, September 19, 1995.
  - Item 28: GOP Agrees on Medicaid Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: Conn. Surcharge System Upheld, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, September 14, 1995.
  - Item 30: Calif. Plan to Adopt Bidding Strategy, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, September 11, 1995.
  - Item 31: HCFA Drops Capital-Payment Hike, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, September 9, 1995.
  - Item 32: HMNO Growth May Be a Mixed Blessing: Study, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Louise Kertesz
  - Item 33: Judge Blocks Giuliani Plan to Sell Hospital in Queens, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Elisabeth Rosenthal
    Notes: New York Times, September 29, 1995.
  - Item 34: Clinton Assails GOP's Plans on Health Care, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Robert Pear
    Notes: New York Times, September 30, 1995.
  - Item 35: Senate GOP Plan for Medicare Uses Benefit Cutbacks, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, September 28, 1995.
  - Item 36: House GOP Plan Doubles Premiums of Medicare Users, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, September 22, 1995.
  - Item 37: Republican Blitz Shakes Congress, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: R. W. Apple, Jr.
    Notes: New York Times, September 23, 1995.
  - Item 38: Medicare Plus' or 'Medicare Choice,' the Essence Is All the Same, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: New York Times
  - Item 39: California Refuses to Bail Out Los Angeles, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Seth Mydans
    Notes: September 15, 1995.
  - Item 40: Protest Disrupts Hospital, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: September 19, 1995.
  - Item 41: GOP Announces Plan to Overhaul Medicare System, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 42: An Exam for Home Health Care, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Milt Freudenheim
  - Item 43: Not Selling, Three Hospitals, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: David Firestone
  - Item 44: WellPoint Purchase of Health Systems Is Approved by Key California Agency, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Rhonda L. Rundle
    Notes: The Wall Street Journal, September 8, 1995.
  - Item 45: S.1307-A Lack (same as A.7933 Rules/Weisenberg), Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Continuing Care Connection Legislative Update. Special edition
  - Item 46: Code Committee Approves Nursing Home Code Changes, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Continuing Care Connection Legislative Update. v.2:no.16 (1995:Aug. 2)
  - Item 47: Six Governors Urge Change in Formula for Distributing Federal Medicaid Dollars, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 48: Comments Due on Proposed Rulemaking for Governor's 16-Point Regulatory Reform Plan, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 49: HANYS Urges Pataki Administration and Congressional Delegation to Fight Medicaid/Medicare Redistribution, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.26 (1995:June 30).
  - Item 50: Congress Returns to Address Reductions in Medicare and Medicaid, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: HANYS News, v.27:no.28 (1995:July 14).
  - Item 51: Congress Focuses on Medicaid, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Skyline News, 95-15 (1995:July 17)
  - Item 52: NYC Groups to Form CHIN, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Skyline News, 95-16 (1995:July 31)
  - Item 53: New Report Finds Workplace Innovations in Health Care Have Mixed Effects on Quality of Care, Employee Satisfaction and Cost Saving, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Economic Policy Institute
    Notes: Press release
  - Item 54: Enrollment Suspended, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Crains's New York Business
    Notes: Crain's New York Business, July 31, 1995
  - Item 55: Hospitals Trim Staffs After State Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 56: Nonprofits Uniting toKnit Network For Medical Data, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 57: Computerization: Health Care at the Forefront, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Business and Health, July 1995
  - Item 58: Health Care Workforce Trends, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Labor Research Association
    Notes: July, 1995.
  - Item 59: Certificate of Need Intake Log, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: June 1, 1995.
  - Item 60: News at Deadline, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, July 20, 1995.
  - Item 61: Currents, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 62: Inside Track, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 63: Insurance for Life, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Hospitals and Health Networks, July 5, 1995.
  - Item 64: Enrollment/Disenrollment Patterns for Medicare Risk Plans, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: July 15, 1995.
  - Item 65: Simon Says, Join Us!, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Ellyn R. Spragins
  - Item 66: Long-Term Care Insurance in 1993, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Susan Coronel; Diane Fulton
    Notes: June 30, 1995.
  - Item 67: News at Deadline, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, July 31, 1995.
  - Item 68: GNYHA, Insurers to Develop CHIN, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: John Morrissey
  - Item 69: Medicare PPOs Subject to Senate Panel Hearing, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: J. Duncan Moore, Jr.
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, July 24, 1995.
  - Item 70: House GOP Unveils Medicare Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 71: HMOs Put Satisfaction Data to Workd, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Joyce Jensen
  - Item 72: HMO Stocks Fall With Fla. Medicaid Rate Cut, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Sandy Lutz; Jay Greene
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, July 3, 1995.
  - Item 73: Hospital Profits Stable Despite Market Changes, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: David Burda
  - Item 74: Hospital Mergers Slip in First Quarter, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 75: Complaints Lead to Suspension of an HMO Run by Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Ian Fisher
    Notes: New York Times, July 26, 1995.
  - Item 76: To Compete, Hospitals Get Hoteliers' Service Lessons, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Esther B. Fein
    Notes: New York Times, July 24, 1995.
  - Item 77: Medicare, Turning 30, Won't Be What It Was, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Robin Toner; Robert Pear
    Notes: New York Times, July 23, 1995.
  - Item 78: Important Dates in Medicare History, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Monica Borkowski
  - Item 79: The Debate: Free to Choose, Or Is It Coercion?, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: The New York Times
  - Item 80: The Politics: Behind the Fight, A Broader Issue, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 81: Bill on Gap In Health Care Gets Boost At Hearing, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Adam Clymer
    Notes: New York Times, July 19, 1995.
  - Item 82: GOP Proposing Greater Choices About Medicare, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, July 17, 1995.
  - Item 83: Bill Takes On Health Issues In Small Steps, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, July 14, 1995.
  - Item 84: Congress Passes GOP's Budget Balancing Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: David E. Rosenbaum
    Notes: New York Times, June 30, 1995.
  - Item 85: IUD Launches Major Coordinated Bargaining Effort for 63,000 Kaiser Permanente Workers, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: IUD Action
    Notes: IUD Action, July 5, 1995.
  - Item 86: 1995 National Ambulatory Care Survey, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Tribrook
  - Item 87: Leading Academic Hospital, Squeaking By, Seeks Merger, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, July 8, 1995.
  - Item 88: HMO's Refusing Emergency Claims, Hospitals Assert, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, July 9, 1995.
  - Item 89: Study Shows Hospitals Dealing With Fewer But Sicker Patients, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 90: N.Y. Presbyterian Talks Partnership, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, July 17, 1995.
  - Item 91: NY Hospitals Discuss Merger, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Crain News Service
  - Item 92: Effort to Drop Stark Fraud, Abuse Rules Makes Dems Angry, Providers Happy, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, October 16, 1995.
  - Item 93: GOP Governor Opposition Jeopardizes Senate Plan, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 94: NY Court Order Bars Medicaid Cost Shifting, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Karen Pallarito
  - Item 95: GOP Picks Up AMA Support as Medicare Plan Advances, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 96: HealthSouth To Take Lead in Ambulatory Sector, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 97: Technology Keeps Food Costs on Diet, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Charlotte Snow
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, October 9, 1995.
  - Item 98: Full Speed Ahead with Integration, For Better or Worse, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Mary Chris Jaklevic
  - Item 99: Providers Look Ahead With Fear at Medicare 'Look-Back' Provision, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, October 2, 1995.
  - Item 100: Credit Agency Says Hospitals Face Hazards From Proposed Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Holcomb B. Noble
    Notes: New York Times, November 3, 1995.
  - Item 101: Medical Centers May Lease City Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Vivian S. Toy
    Notes: New York Times, October 29, 1995.
  - Item 102: Senate Softens Some Edges in Passing, 52-47, Its Version of Vast Budget Cutbacks, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Jerry Gray
    Notes: New York Times, October 28, 1995.
  - Item 103: Outline of the Republican Proposals on the Budget, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 104: New York Lifts Rule Forcing The Poor Into Managed Care, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 105: Vote is 227 to 203, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, October 27, 1995.
  - Item 106: Pressured by Moderates, GOP Leaders Agree to Keep Strict Rules on Nursing Homes, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 107: Mayor Offers 3 Hospitals for Lease, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 108: House Votes to Curb Costs of Medicare by $270 Billion; President Promises a Veto, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, October 20, 1995.
  - Item 109: Senate Panel, in Party Voting, Backs a $245 Billion Tax Cut, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Keith Bradsher
  - Item 110: Beneath Surface, Health Care Plan is Offering Boons, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Martin Gottlieb; Robert Pear
    Notes: New York Times, October 15, 1995.
  - Item 111: AMA Defends Its Decision To Back Medicare Proposals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, October 12, 1995.
  - Item 112: AMA Backing Republicans In Plan to Overhaul Medicare, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: New York Times, October 11, 1995.
  - Item 113: Medicare Bill Passed By House Would End Egalitarian Approach, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Laurie McGinley; Christopher Georges
  - Item 114: Slimming Down Medicare, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 115: Hospital Sale Memo Due, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- RN Division News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Headlines, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: AJN (American Journal of Nursing)
    Notes: American Journal of Nursing, November, 1995.
  - Item 2: Proof of the Tight Rein on Health Premiums, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Business and Health, November, 1995
  - Item 3: Health-Care Paychecks Won't Get Much Bigger, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: The New Variety in Managed Care, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Helen Lippman
  - Item 5: Skyline News, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: 95-24 (1995:Nov. 30)
  - Item 6: Morale Hits New Low, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, December 11, 1995
  - Item 7: NY To Dump Rate-Setting System, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Texas Orders Charter to Pay Fine, Offfer Free Care to Medicare Kids, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: GOP Group Tries to Win Extra Dollars for Medicaid, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Iver Peterson
    Notes: New York Times, December 28, 1995
  - Item 10: Mayor Meets With Silver On State Cuts, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Clifford J. Levy
    Notes: New York Times, December 19, 1995
  - Item 11: Doctors Say HMO's Limit What They Can Tell Patients, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 21, 1995
  - Item 12: Giuliani at Odds With Governor Over Benefits for the City, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Steven Lee Myers
    Notes: New York Times, December 16, 1995
  - Item 13: Budget Sails Before Federal Winds, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: James Dao
  - Item 14: Pataki Offers Medicaid Cuts That Could Close Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 17, 1995
  - Item 15: Pataki Proposes Closing of a Brooklyn Hospital, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 14, 1995
  - Item 16: Challanging Giuliani, Council Attacks Sale of Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 12, 1995
  - Item 17: Upbeat Estimates May Give Leeway For Budget Deal, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: New York Times, December 11, 1995
  - Item 18: Drop in Hospital Cost Shifting Showing Up On Bottom Line, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, November 20, 1995
  - Item 19: Moody's Downgrades 4 New York Hospitals, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: For the Record, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, November 13, 1995
  - Item 21: Day of the Per Diem, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Judge Sides With Nurses in Labor Dispute, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Modern Healthcare, October 30, 1995
  - Item 23: The Move East, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 24: PacifiCare Uses Medicare Risk to Expand to New States, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 25: FHP's Acquistion of TakeCare Fueled Growth, 1995; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)